Contact

Brahmanbaria , Bangladesh +8801794614628 (Mobile) mdranasarkar909@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-rana-mia-4b9b33259 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Bootstrap
JavaScript
WordPress

MD. Rana Mia

Web Development at Brahmanbaria Freelancing-BFTI

Brahmanbaria, Chattogram, Bangladesh

Summary

Hi!

Hello! I am Rana I am a web developer with over Two years of experience.

I am passionate about building websites that people love using. I enjoy the challenge of creating beautiful designs that are both clear and easy to navigate through.

I am study honor's second year at National University in Bangladesh.

Experience

Brahmanbaria Freelancing-BFTI 2 years 1 month

Freelance Web Developer May 2022 - Present (1 year)

Brahmanbaria District, Chattogram, Bangladesh

Web Development April 2021 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Brahmanbaria, Chattogram, Bangladesh

Education

National University of Bangladesh

Bachelor of Business Study, Accounting and Business/Management · (July 2021)

Kazi Mohammad Shofiqul Islam University (2019 - 2021)

Brahmanbaria Freelancing Training Institute
Computer Typography and Composition Equipment Operator